<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ashish Tiwari</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 22:06:05 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 22:06:05 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cycling from Andheri to Madh Island !</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;trek-photography&quot;&gt;#Trek #Photography&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;cycling-from-andheri-to-madh-island&quot;&gt;Cycling from Andheri to Madh Island&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day moring me and my friend abhijeet cycled to Varsoa beach. While we were chilling out we saw an island(madh) in front of us and instantly planned to go there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We opened Google-Maps and planned everything to reach there. There is a shortcut which you can take to reach quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;reach varsoa village jetty&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;take boat - 3rs per person/cycle for madh-island jetty.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;reach madh-island jetty in 3min.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;take bus for Madh Island.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, we planned something else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;andheri-highway-flyover-to-andheri-versoa-linking-road&quot;&gt;Andheri Highway Flyover to Andheri-Versoa linking road.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A one fine Saturday morning at around 6:30am,  &lt;a href=&quot;/&quot;&gt;Pritanka&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ashishtiwari.me/&quot;&gt;Me&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/abhijeet.ydv&quot;&gt;Abhijeet&lt;/a&gt; took our cycles with us and met at a point. We thought of going to a different place where we haven’t been before for cycling. And then suddnely one of us  said “lets go to madh island via marve beach”. On hearing this we just saw at each other, smiled and what happened next was searching route to reach there, optimization of routes, after a 10min route discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We three bikers started our biking session from,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Andheri east - western express highway- Sagar hotel.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Took a road from regency in Andheri east, came out on Andheri west highway road.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Took a straight road of Andheri west highway connecting to link road.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a soothing atmosphere. Already it has rained at 5:30am in the morning. The smell of the soil was so soothing. As it was Saturday morning 7am there were hardly vehicle on the road. It was so cloudly that gave us doubt that it would rain now while cycling. Like this riding and indicating directions to each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;map--andheri-to-madh-island&quot;&gt;MAP : Andheri to Madh Island&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/xngnHvXFtgnjZwEULjmxnuGFlj4b8AwbiU3hRaXOUac7EM7nkM_xd7CaSLknmWqb5uqzzd78pA=w1280-h800-rw-no&quot; alt=&quot;map pic&quot; class=&quot;center-image img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;andheri-jogeshwari-goregaon-malad-link-road&quot;&gt;Andheri-Jogeshwari-Goregaon-Malad link road&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We passed Andheri, Jogeshwari, Goregaon.
Priyanka stopped at a point she said, &lt;em&gt;”
It so hard to paddle this long. Sometimes the legs become numb.&lt;/em&gt; We took a short break near &lt;strong&gt;Infinity Mall&lt;/strong&gt;. But there was a quest of reaching to the destination that we kept going we three of us. Halting taking selfies, taking few sip of water, motivating each other we kept moving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We again checked how much is left and it was just half hour more. We were so near and we were so excited. we again paddled to rush to the place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;malvani-to-marve-beach&quot;&gt;Malvani To Marve Beach&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We took a turn to Malavani Road. The road was so bad, full of pothholes, Bumping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somehow we entered a road which looked so amazing and smooth. Trees on both the side. Here &lt;strong&gt;we reached marve beach&lt;/strong&gt; the first in the line of &lt;strong&gt;Aksa beach&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Mud island jetty&lt;/strong&gt;. We took a look at the serene beauty. There were boats from marve taking people to other side ( Manori Jetty ). We could also see a golden top of a temple which we came to know is the Vipassana Temple. We also understood that on that side is the gorai creek and nearby is the essel world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The three of us have not had breakfast before we left home. And this was the first destination that we reached from where we were very near to our final stop “Madh Island”. We had a breakfast there, idli, vada and a hot tea made us refreshing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/TxUrMjulr8Pf1aNRwM2GgqZoQLVtGBge5stLcO4Vg6_tZJtlBl1dUEE_pMA2m9OMPlnWo9itig=w1280-h800-rw-no&quot; alt=&quot;team pic&quot; class=&quot;center-image img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;marve-beach-to-aksa-beach&quot;&gt;Marve Beach To Aksa Beach&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thereon we took our cycles and moved further. Again a beautiful road. We saw there &lt;strong&gt;Sathya Sai Institute of biotechnology&lt;/strong&gt;. As we moved further, we found many road-board stating its a land of indian coastal land. Further we also saw camps of INS Hamla.
Then what we saw next was a serene beauty. A road full of trees on both the sides. It was such that from both the sides trees are growing and they are getting merged in the middle creating a roof along the entire road. Passing by that route, we reached aksa beach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of us threw our cycle on sand and rushed to wet ourself in the water. There were very few people on the beaches.  We were playing in the water, taking pictures. Then we sat on the beach and enjoyed listening to the waves, the cool air and the calm surrounding. We complimented this setup with a refreshing nariyal pani.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;aksa-beach-to-madh-island-and-madh-island-jetty&quot;&gt;Aksa Beach to Madh Island and Madh Island Jetty&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And with that we moved further to &lt;strong&gt;Madh Island Jetty&lt;/strong&gt;. Again the route from aksa beach ro the madh island jetty was amazing and protected by natural roof provided by trees on both the side. Passing by this we finally reached the last point Madh Island Jetty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;madh-island-jetty-to-versoa-village&quot;&gt;Madh Island Jetty to Versoa Village&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We took a boat there, put our cycles on the boat costing Rs.3 per person/cycle. Within 5mins of journey on the boat we reached Versova Village. Again we boarded our cycles from the boat and began our journey back to home I.e Andheri east western express highway where we started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;versoa-village-to-andheri--via-4-bunglow-road-&quot;&gt;Versoa Village to Andheri ( via 4-bunglow road )&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The return journey from versova was quite hectic and hot. It was around 11:15am, the cloudy weather which we enjoyed in the morning has changed to bright sunlight, sucking our energy and making us more tired.
Finally after a rigorous cycling of 3-4hrs we reached our respective homes by 12:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scorched, tired with countless happiness. The amazing cycling session from Andheri to Madh Island and back to Andheri came to an end with good memories and amazing experience to be cherished in our lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yay!! I reached home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;:( Now I’ve to go to office due to an E-Mail which was sent by &lt;strong&gt;Project Manager&lt;/strong&gt; 2days back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;what-is-next-plan-&quot;&gt;WHAT IS NEXT PLAN ??&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lets-go-to-gateway-of-india-&quot;&gt;LETS GO TO GATEWAY OF INDIA 😎&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/post/2016/06/22/cycling-from-andheri-to-madh-island.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/post/2016/06/22/cycling-from-andheri-to-madh-island.html</guid>
        
        <category>photography</category>
        
        <category>cycling</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trek - An Achievement!</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;trek-photography&quot;&gt;#Trek #Photography&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trek&lt;/strong&gt; - A concept which holds different meaning for different people. For some its a way of meeting new people. A way of connectivity sometimes people of same mind frame meet here which either bond them as a professional partner or a life partner or a Friend for life. If not friend, its remembered as a trek experience which always resides in the persons memory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some, its a way of fighting with their own weakness and overcoming them. Trek motivates them to move forward, take the challenge, go ahead against the gravity and ascend. Though for that time the notion is to move forward and reach the top. But it changes your mindset of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://drscdn.500px.org/photo/9008106/q%3D80_m%3D1500/69b5f2097de3b305f9e60f6052baaace&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;center-image img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some, its a feeling of &lt;strong&gt;conquership&lt;/strong&gt;. just imagine how &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shivaji&quot;&gt;shivaji maharaj&lt;/a&gt; have conquered these &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shivaji%27s_forts&quot;&gt;sahyadri forts&lt;/a&gt;, the idea of making way out of way which is not at all possible to think. Some go for trek just to get the feel of conquership. Obviously, climbing the mountain for so many hours and reaching the top, its a great feel. Conquered this, not really but atleast mentally. Being so many forts in sahyadri itself, trekking them all is a big achievement of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forts being at such a great height, the place is extremely away from the city’s crowd and pollution. hence a good place to calm your mind giving you a peaceful atmosphere, so much greenary around makes your soul feel in heaven. Those red soil, gives you a natural manicure. The feel of the soil itself is so good. you go through woods, see so many creatures of different kind. Enjoy the waterfall. Ponds, cisterns full of water and so clean to drink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You get to listen to so many sounds of birds and creatures. You get to see birds of different kind. Villages people who are so humble, always ready to guide and help. In crisis, they even take care of your health and feed you. The food is so delicious, a simple home made indian food. Just lovely feeling again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The journey from base of the fort to the top and again coming back to base itself is amazing. A complete package explaining different concept of life. While ascending, our heartbeat increases, legs become numb, thirst that never goes.. All these feelings just vanishes when you reach top of the mountain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A 360 degree view of the mountain ranges, wind moving around us, drizzles  and fog during monsoon, even a walk in the cloud, a feeling of freedom, what more do you want in your life than this feeling. All the pain, thirst goes away and we became one with the nature. what more do we want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This feeling resides such a deep in hearts, that the thirst for nature never goes and again we are back to it in the form of next trek, same or new fort, sahyadri or himachal or any.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall any experience that we get from trek is an achievement in some or the other form and hence we are attracted to it so much that we want to do it again and again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;be-positive-be-enthusiastic-keep-trekking-keep-achieving&quot;&gt;Be positive. Be enthusiastic. Keep trekking. Keep achieving.&lt;/h1&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/post/2016/06/20/trek-an-achievement.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/post/2016/06/20/trek-an-achievement.html</guid>
        
        <category>photography</category>
        
        <category>trek</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hampi to Pattadakal and Pattadkal to Aihole!</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;hampi&quot;&gt;Hampi&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hampi (Hampe) is a village in northern Karnataka, India. It was one of the richest and largest cities in the world during its prime. The name Hampi can also mean “champion”. It is located within the ruins of the city of Vijayanagara, the former capital of the Vijayanagara Empire. Predating the city of Vijayanagara, Hampi continues to be an important religious centre, housing the Virupaksha Temple and several other monuments belonging to the old city. The ruins are a UNESCO World Heritage Site, listed as the Group of Monuments at Hampi. According to statistics of 2014, Hampi is the most searched historical place in Karnataka on Google. The empire boasted a massive army comprising close to a million men. In around 1500 AD Vijaynagar had about 500,000 inhabitants (supporting 0.1% of the global population during 1440-1540), making it the second largest city in the world after Peking-Beijing and almost thrice the size of Paris.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://drscdn.500px.org/photo/150562951/q%3D80_m%3D1500_k%3D1/51b3e4a33fb500f4728d5e3c712572a0&quot; alt=&quot;Picture description&quot; class=&quot;center-image img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hampi — traditionally known as Pampa-kshetra, Kishkindha-kshetra or Bhaskara-kshetra — is derived from Pampa, which is the old name of the Tungabhadra River (also Pampa was Lord Bhrumah’s daughter, who was later married to Lord Shiva) on whose southern banks the city is built. The name “Hampi” is an anglicized version of the Kannada Hampe (derived from Pampa). Over the years, it has also been referred to as Vijayanagara and Virupakshapura (from Virupaksha, the patron deity of the Vijayanagara rulers).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The emperor Ashoka’s Minor Rock Edicts in Nittur &amp;amp; Udegolan (both in Bellary district) suggest that this region was part of the Ashokan kingdom during the 3rd century BC. A Brahmi inscription and a terracotta seal dating to the 2nd century CE were also recovered from the excavation site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first settlements in Hampi date from 1 CE.
Immediately before the rise of the Vijayanagara kings, the region was probably in the hands of chiefs of Kampili, now a small town, 19 km east of Hampi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kampili was said to have been founded by Gayathri Giri of Annar bara. Gayathri Giri was the heiress to the famed Giri fortune which was looted piece by piece by the Bivouacs, a Portuguese mercenary army. Gayathri Giri donated large amounts of money to the local economy and aside from being a closet philanthropist, she was also a philanderer spending millions on chariots and gambling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;pattadkal&quot;&gt;Pattadkal&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pattadakal also spelled Paṭṭadakallu is a World Heritage site, a village and an important tourist centre in the state of Karnataka and is located on the left bank of the Malaprabha River in Bagalkot district and is 22 km from Badami and 514 km from Bangalore. It is 22 km from Badami and about 10 km from Aihole, both of which are well known for Chalukya monuments. The Pre-Chalukya historical and Archaeological site Bachinagudda is also near Pattadakal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pattadakal is a great centre of Chalukya art and architecture, noted for its temples and inscriptions. According to inscriptions, the place was known by the names Kisuvolal (Red Town - mostly mountains near pattadakal gave this name), Raktapura, Pattada Kisuvolal. The literary work Hammira Kavya of 1540 quotes the place as Pattashilapura and Hammirapura. It has been mentioned in the 11th and 12th century inscriptions, as well as in the literary work Singirajapurana of 1500 and Hammira Kavya as the place where the Chalukya kings were crowned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://drscdn.500px.org/photo/150561767/q%3D80_m%3D1500_k%3D1/961b67aef14f4f527374347779efee6d&quot; alt=&quot;Picture description&quot; class=&quot;center-image img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://wikipedia.com/&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt; - Wikipedia&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/photography/post/2016/05/17/hampi-pattadkal-badami-trip.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/photography/post/2016/05/17/hampi-pattadkal-badami-trip.html</guid>
        
        <category>photography</category>
        
        <category>trek</category>
        
        <category>camera</category>
        
        <category>Canon-1200D</category>
        
        
        <category>photography</category>
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World!</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;metallica-helloworld&quot;&gt;#metallica #helloworld&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet another blog post on &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.io/&quot;&gt;github.io&lt;/a&gt; with #metallica poster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-Cwtqahoj6qA/U6MXUu4y9OI/AAAAAAAAE-I/h_6rVKosuWo/s1600/metallica_kalaghoda.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Picture description&quot; class=&quot;center-image img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/post/2016/05/16/hello-world-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/post/2016/05/16/hello-world-post.html</guid>
        
        <category>greetings</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Using Django As A Microframework, Like Flask.</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;django-as-microframework&quot;&gt;#django as microframework&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today me and my friend were discussing about &lt;strong&gt;flask&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;django&lt;/strong&gt;. We were arguing over flask is microframework and django is not and all other topics related to pros and cons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not going to start comparing these two great frameworks, but I’ve created a django-microsite project for a test.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I break down the settings.py, urls.py, views.py in one file. I googled about all these and finally achieved it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;requirements&quot;&gt;requirements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.djangoproject.com/&quot;&gt;django&lt;/a&gt; can be installed by using &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;pip install django&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;create &lt;strong&gt;django-microsite.py&lt;/strong&gt; file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;#########################################
# A Pythonic Django Microsite example
# Inspired by Flask and Bottle framework
#########################################

import sys
from django.conf import settings

settings.configure(
 DEBUG=True,
 SECRET_KEU=&#39;secretkeygoeshere&#39;,
 ROOT_URLCONF = __name__,
 MIDDLEWARE_CLASSES = (
     &#39;django.middleware.common.CommonMiddleware&#39;,
     &#39;django.middleware.clickjacking.XFrameOptionsMiddleware&#39;,
        &#39;django.middleware.clickjacking.XFrameOptionsMiddleware&#39;,
 ),
)

from django.conf.urls import url
from django.http import HttpResponse
from django.shortcuts import render_to_response

def index(request):
 return HttpResponse(&quot;Hey see this! It&#39;s working.&quot;)

urlpatterns = (
 url(r&#39;^$&#39;, index,name=&quot;index_page&quot;),
)

if __name__ == &quot;__main__&quot;:
 from django.core.management import execute_from_command_line
 execute_from_command_line(sys.argv)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might be thinking, how to run this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a django project :) simply use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;runserver&lt;/code&gt; command.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;python django-microsite.py runserver&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;working code can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ashish2py/django-microsite&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;reference&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ashish2py/django-microsite&quot;&gt;django project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ashish2py/django-microsite&quot;&gt;django configurations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/post/2016/02/10/django-as-micro-web-framework.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/post/2016/02/10/django-as-micro-web-framework.html</guid>
        
        <category>python</category>
        
        <category>django</category>
        
        <category>microframework</category>
        
        <category>flask</category>
        
        <category>code</category>
        
        <category>snippet</category>
        
        <category>github</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Canon-1200D, new gadget in my list!</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;flipkart-bigbillionday-canon-camera-photography-nationalpark&quot;&gt;#flipkart #bigbillionday #canon #camera #photography #nationalpark&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One year ago, same day &lt;strong&gt;Flipkart’s Big Billion Day Sale&lt;/strong&gt; started on Monday with mobile phones and tablets topping the charts of the biggest deals on offer.
But I was looking for something else which upgrades my old canon camera and I found Canon-1200D for 17,000/-.
Really ? Yes!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One week ago, same camera was for 29,000/- and now It’s for 17,000. I purchased it!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flipkart took 2week to deliver the camera, because there were some chaos going on in order delivery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been going crazy to take images so visited Sanjay Gandhi National Park and few &lt;strong&gt;Treks&lt;/strong&gt;.
Among the pictures taken in this frenzy are the ones below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;signature-spider--national-park&quot;&gt;Signature Spider : National Park&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn’t know the name untill one of my friend told me about this #signature spider.
For me it’s a &lt;strong&gt;WEB DEVELOPER&lt;/strong&gt; who don’t forget to mention copyrights on his web-site. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ooj7qZwl58-kAhdyjAR5fjyw9BrFKffVcWOEpRVFuG73pLO8WOWaNvXu43fgRWWSK4Qa0Oc19EaO9gOfHteJHErRE1epH42hP4sGsWQb4J8UCNgDEz_KK89WJ-hZJSib08nXz0cmHfvpCKYykRTQW8Q90EfDGg8G1dD4u9BA-ayT6CvjP9CTC6xbdV_1Kv1NNP548DVdme3YlJJolfrVE7TSkcYenRAxMkeO7EPcuitesHNmIUG9BV481JvkPTZD54T-nEpMfQJPeNiBYNMRKCoA0it6unA1Ua3H8Rx8W3I4jl498HEziiHxxDmvlwCBlPvpbDySjgJFEG-5ctPxX2YYS4V_hQ0ysF9ETg_BTQyP0U-7jWGuIGlJFm-VqyFBsTP3tsVmBs2C0vhY-oqv0cqJMRzZqw1_h8zsKTqARxKYdAPLEMbWGH8LC3Fdk4B4RCRAlkVHnYIsiTKtRL7D_7dPd5X8NRWOkCsjrDpmMUtqBlncOeL-Pcr_NIMRfWgoq-vmPGYZNYkImX1xj06bs9AY-n7J5hGjorQhJqFN6-JbsNi6Mq33UyUyTyeQ_PqtL5FiaNYu1RnRYKpVO5loT7G_trwgW1o=w1024-h644-no&quot; alt=&quot;Picture description&quot; class=&quot;center-image img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This spider weaves four zig zag stripes in its web, and holds its legs together in pairs. It holds its legs in pairs to disguise itself as a four legged creature; it does this to not appear to look like a spider.
There are 75 different species of this spider but they all look the same. Their colours vary in between their stripes but they all keep the black and yellow stripes, They distribute also Sri Lanka, Maldives,India, Pakistan.Their habitats are Moist Deciduous forests in the sunny parts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Argiope_(spider)&quot;&gt;More Info&lt;/a&gt; - Wikipedia&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;ant-hill--murud-beach&quot;&gt;Ant Hill : Murud Beach&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A nest in the form of a mound built by ants or termites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CaJqUa5gmBSoFkmEs1hylF9wC9fzYkBJsWDi7CCGA3sajyMiHF0k_IHgPKCx8UxpKDmzXNok5IXZgRxBvUpwWtzdZ-jjvbPFTPwji8-vNoX71OPkTBvSWoWJS9JzK7eF0iYF7vRpy453RDRDSymKkLxs5hu6sd0VOOl7kdifdnF3MqhfwHsnVxGrUihpY6fxWAa85XLXkNqopwhXm2LBzJCwfV4n2KeslhtzzJltLfB4AL-f1f4BRz8F9OCOgAUKrqcCN-EyM_uzXGVBpdG5q4gMEX6NgItpo745me6JT9ctZji6N8BclVSvodBwM8xtEAjovYIM_DRFCA5z9y8cn1X6cWzoABkTzEjhA5S8PwD-_vMEZjQ40TfCNU8pmWjIfJhMYa9YJENFyfwTkz0sFakQNIDEFHZ5QW8UW7pO8tP6BquIu9bGflHjnnit9jQeNKGXCjuoIBagjzEhogO1q9jPZNeSSI9-g_s2EgyMcMR3y5rAhE6_ImsK_zGYMmbIiCX6SLTrDTNiWHTbW-7dti0n5pUp5DlhIvW5-ijyhXg9yr2tHhpPbqdZCy-HDYxsX23gD-Ob5nTjVjbboIEC5_nbqieXZ3E=w967-h644-no&quot; alt=&quot;Picture description&quot; class=&quot;center-image img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;sudhagadh-trek--pali&quot;&gt;Sudhagadh Trek : Pali&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trail to Sudhagad is a stairway to heaven in monsoon. You’re surrounded by highly saturated green, with unimaginably beautiful weather. Atop the peak is a 50 acre plateau with undulating green meadows. It’s the perfect place to lie in grass and stare at the clouds with your friends or family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trek is technically a one-day trek, but stretching it to two, with overnight camping at the wada (old village house with a huge open space in the centre) will help you squeeze the best out of the trek. Also, to cover the entire plateau, it takes around 2-3 hours, so it becomes a little exhausting if done as a single day trek.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zqdU2fAAqrJu9JIQy8aJ7CQ9oFXTDfsV7p8rQsTscLCjG_5wB80WV7o_mRNN8d64qyfEs10xHmola_nQEXQ7FQcIeCE-4l9cHjnDrfN8l-4ZRIAX3iILLa88_N89Np3Pm_cGADW1L1LTgcHX4gTrmtGjOEgOEuP5lvDXSkOCQdiY77xtVKYm6HcFAlrPjUzBMXaSZaMPvo0u-Nutokgo_H7aOY4d16vRlJ_4dYP9ic0W1KAUhRHUF6hBTBfypRtqhoUFyc5DFLeJrbMsacSBaynxMOXam0GJJnB4omqp31BAy_rqTq1LfwRDKlQ2Bs3tTsWfqLW0WD-lPJUEo0vri4fbv1vitHZSsA4WYxKs2rNKMw3p_05Z91BurEgMo9mRJ2s6J9YKxmMEqmbuCpsftXMnklnVMBhC5c0wPgbRTEmcSL8ZVISlau4zaSOgSA7WV_xj2YCbOVPKM1TNYprCyyNOnKbXuqAO-nHJVbJeyZfn81VNtBbcYXkgN9neJwBFRyLLn_w_a0QxRIA0_QV5fYWqQKuvLuGesH7QgOyDB1zNBNy522aO00OltlUwmEZlqLToic68U5YwR0F8Y_Xz1icIaCnKBIg=w967-h644-no&quot; alt=&quot;Picture description&quot; class=&quot;center-image img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;sunset--sudhagadh&quot;&gt;Sunset : Sudhagadh&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunrise with milky fog at left corner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/cTZMYVqQwtFJqvnrH9uaP9EOnLWdms4F-5UQsio475qywt2zksN3bjRLLqOOXziVUM24RCiseglQaHW74JYQteNgWt4o89mMO3rSz6J6_-0h7Db0q-ArV_OQK_Vk8677UDNCQ1D_7GxkE3WTAeu81HJRvmjJiCzpmRYfGfgrPSNVfzTrM424ZW7m79Xc7CVlZNX6lX8Zu_MuQY47mKdauwMk30w7W_vk04qoPQpVPKxW1e7lieeyT_AMtZUwbb3xqo6AMbG9k1y24ey50yiQyRUTisxahp6ICNyNYwbvXq1UZ967kn3vdkmaxIIcu3popBQ8CCLa7aTjhKca4mfzZQA8DnZsCpIPJMkdDeIikA-IQDLrx9piuRM6CKjrO_W0HHwHr60uBUU_5YTqSGcuzfRjDmbODa411C4riIDiyZz8gielZLNth3lf1JtJqI0cJhgLMx56JkhmQJOuWcBeJm8zOdeKIeyvFCHjRn-iQGdHH1kSEci79QXGUm-ypEhUU8VsydaY9R6IQZ1Ix3ETOJSp-XDAEtznjO2rAgiwGFsVacTOopx710XY1Xm1QV073DuQi4Q6XvWA1uDt4kQ4fa7fmPF6wzk=w1280-h275-no&quot; alt=&quot;Picture description&quot; class=&quot;center-image img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sudhagadh is one of my favorite trek destination. I’m planning to write a separate post for Sudhagadh Trek.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/photography/post/2015/10/07/new-gadget-in-my-list.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/photography/post/2015/10/07/new-gadget-in-my-list.html</guid>
        
        <category>photography</category>
        
        <category>trek</category>
        
        <category>camera</category>
        
        <category>Canon-1200D</category>
        
        
        <category>photography</category>
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
